Guide to the Stanford University, Medical Center, Health Care Education Network, Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Medical Center, Health Care Education Network, videorecordings
1990-1994
V0247
Stanford University. Medical Center. Health Care Education Network.
12 Linear feet
Beta source tapes for various films produced by the Health Care Education Network; topics include Lucile Salter Packard Children's Hospital, organ transplantation, organ donation, cancer, psychiatry services, marketing, orientation to the hospital, Stanford Blood Center, intensive care units, cardiovascular services, bone marrow transplantation, and several interviews with patients and doctors.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
Access: tapes will need to be transferred to another format to be viewed.
Description of the Collection
Beta source tapes for various films produced by the Health Care Education Network; topics include Lucile Salter Packard Children's Hospital, organ transplantation, organ donation, cancer, psychiatry services, marketing, orientation to the hospital, Stanford Blood Center, intensive care units, cardiovascular services, bone marrow transplantation, and several interviews with patients and doctors.
Access Terms
Lucile Salter Packard Children's Hospital.; Stanford Blood Center.; Stanford University. Hospital.; Stanford University. Medical Center. Health Care Education Network.; Donation of organs, tissues, etc.; Hospital care.; Medical care.; Videorecordings.
Collection Contents
- Videos, Accession ARCH-2001-294 (Box 1-10)
  - 4th Annual Bone Marrow Transplantation Reunion, edited master, 1992 Oct 6; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - Bone Marrow 5th Reunion, edited master, 1993 Sep 14; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - How Does Medicine Work? part 3, What Is An X-Ray, edited master, 1991 Oct 1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - Invision 93, edited master, 1993 Jan 15; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - Marketing at Stanford University Hospital, edited master, 1993 Jan 29; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - orientation - with special messages, edited master, 1991 Aug 7; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Hospital Community, edited master, 1991 Aug 2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Medical Center Overview SUMC, edited master, 1991 Aug 2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - Lucile Salter Packard Children's Hospital, protection master, 1993 Aug 11; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - How Does Medicine Work? Part 1, edited master, 1991 Oct 1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - Multi Organ Donation Presentation, edited master, 1994 Feb 3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - Systems Development - revised, Ann Fyfe, 1, edited master, 1992 Feb 3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 1)
  - Presents to the Menlo Clinic Additional Perspectives, Version A, edited master, 1993 May 11; 1 videotape (Betacam-SP L) (Box 2)
  - Presents to the Menlo Clinic Additional Perspectives, Version B, edited master, 1993 May 11; 1 videotape (Betacam-SP L) (Box 2)
  - Putting Cancer in Perspective, edited master, 1992 Aug 3; 1 videotape (Betacam-SP L) (Box 2)
  - How to Prevent a Heart Attack, duplication master, 1994 Jan 13; 1 videotape (Betacam-SP L) (Box 3)
  - Lucile Salter Packard Children's Hospital, edited master, 1993 Aug 11; 1 videotape(s) (Digital) (Box 3)
  - Psychiatry Services, edited master, 1994 Jan 21; 1 videotape(s) (Digital) (Box 3)
  - Bone Marrow Transplantation Program Referral Physician Information, edited master, 1990 Nov 27; 1 videotape (Betacam-SP L) (Box 3)
  - Bloopers and Birthday Tape, edited master, 1993 Nov 19; 1 videotape(s) (Digital) (Box 4)
  - CIRU, edited master, 1993 Feb 23; 1 videotape(s) (Digital) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Blood Center, edited master, 1993 Apr 23; 1 videotape(s) (Digital) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Stroke Video, edited master, 1991 Oct 15; 1 videotape(s) (Digital) (Box 4)
  - Thank You for the Gift of Life, edited master, 1993 Mar 23; 1 videotape(s) (Digital) (Box 4)
  - The Liver Transplant Experience, edited master, 1993 Nov 24; 1 videotape(s) (Digital) (Box 4)
  - Tribute to Nurses, edited master, 5/10/93; 1 videotape(s) (Digital) (Box 4)
  - "Prostate Cancer," "Cervical Cancer" and "Stroke," edited master, 1993 Jul 1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 4)
  - HCEN MOTC Recipients & Donors, edited master, 1993 Mar 29; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford University Hospital's Changing Market - Dan Holloway, edited master, 1992 Dec 3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - CIRU at Stanford University Hospital, edited master, 1993 Nov 10; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - Good People Practicing Medicine, edited master, 1994 Feb 1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - Intensive Care Unit for Cardiac Surgery Patients, edited master, 1992 May 6; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - Mary Lou Allen, San Jose Urban Ministry, protection master, 1992 Dec 1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - Mollie Rowe Transplant Interview, edited master, 1992 Oct 29; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - New Mother, New Baby, edited master, 1991 Sep 9; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - Stanford Foothills, edited master, 1992 Feb 6; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - The Stanford Bone Marrow Transplant Program, edited master, 1990 Oct 24; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - "Tribute to Peter Bing," edited master, 1994 Jan 11; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - Understanding Coronary #1, Heart Disease, edited master, 1990 Sep 19; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - HCEN Systems Development-Revised, Ann Fyfe, edited master, 1992 Dec 3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Rehabilitation Services, edited master, 1994 Sep 29; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - BMT Third Reunion, edited master, 1991 Oct 7; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - How Does Medicine Work? Part 2, "What Is A Doctor," edited master, 1991 Oct 1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - International Medical Services at Stanford University Hospital, edited master, 1993 Feb 8; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - Interview with Robert Carlson, M.D., edited master, 1992 May 18; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - "Optical Imaging," edited master, 1992 Feb 6; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - Quitting Smoking - Kenneth Bloem intro, edited master, 1992 May 28; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - Quitting Smoking - Nancy Miller intro, edited master, 1992 May 28; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - SUH highlights, edited master, 1991 Oct 8; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - SUH: The Electrophsiology Experience at Stanford, edited master, 1993 May 28; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - Total Quality Management, edited master, 1994 Feb 3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 6)
  - AICD Implant, Tape 2, 1992 Feb 26; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - CIRU, protection master, 1993 Feb 23; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Rehabilitation Services, duplication master, 1994 Sep 29; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - HCEN Preview Reel, edited master, 1995 May 16; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - Medical-Surgical Intensive Care Unit, edited master, 1993 Jun 14; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - HCEN Bone Marrow Transplantation Program Jack's Experience, 1 edited master, 1990 Jan 27; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - Bone Marrow Transplantation New Clinical Perspectives Highlights, 1, edited master, 1990 Jan 5; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - Palo Alto Centennial, Auction Video (Revised), edited master, 1993 Sep 27; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - Palo Alto Centennial, Auction Video, edited master, 1993 Sep 27; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - Psychiatry Services, edited master, 1994 Oct 4; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - Randy Morris, 1994 Jul 21; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - "Tribute to Peter Bing," duplication master, 1994 Feb 14; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 7)
  - Bone Marrow Transplantation Program, And Now a Little Help from Your Friends, 1, edited master, 1990 Jan 27; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - Intensive Care Unit for Cardac Surgery Patients, Spanish Version, edited master, 1994 Mar 22; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - Medical Surgical ICU, new edited master, 1993 Sep 17; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - Stanford Invision '93 "Old Flickers Segment," sub master, 1993 Jan 14; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - orientation for the Community, edited master, 1991 Sep 12; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - AICD Implant, Tape 1, 1992 Feb 26; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - Angiogram, 35MM Film Transfer, 1992 Jun 15; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - "Preventing Relapse," edited master, 1993 Mar 2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - Randy Morris, reel 2, 1994 Jul 21; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - Randy Morris, Reel 3, 1994 Jul 21; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - Stanford University Hospital, MOTC Twins, edited master, 1994 Apr 29; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 8)
  - A Change Of Heart, edited master, 1992 Jan 15; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
  - International Medical Services at Stanford University Hospital, edited master, 1993 Apr 2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
  - Cardiovascular Services Pt. 2, Interventional Cardiology, edited master, 1992 Jun 24; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
  - Heart Transplantation Overview, edited master, 1992 Jan 16; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 10)
  - Patient TV Interviews, edited master, 1991 May 2; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 10)
  - Putting Cancer in Perspective, Support, edited master, 1992 May 22; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 10)
  - Putting Cancer in Perspective: diagnosis, edited master, 1992 May 7; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 10)
  - Stanford Heart & Heart/Lung Transplant Overview, edited master, 1992 Sep 10; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 10)
  - The Path Video, edited master, 1993 Sep 13; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 10)
  - Putting Cancer in Perspective, The Future, edited master, 1992 May 27; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 11)
  - Cardiovascular Overview Part 1, edited master, 1992 Apr 16; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 11)
  - Putting Cancer In Perspective, Treatment, edited master, 1992 May 21; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 11)